- There you go.
- Thank you.
Hey.
Can I help you?
Yeah.
He says his name's
Patrick Jane.
- Patrick Jane? Really?
- Red John, right?
Wife and daughter?
About a year ago?
Yeah, he's been
off the radar.
Sac P.D. lost track of him
six months ago.
I've never met him.
- Did he say why he came in?
- Just that he wants to talk to you.
Boss, Nevada county
sheriff's office called.
They got a body.
Country road near Malakoff Diggins.
You and Cho check it out.
I'll catch up.
Mr. Jane, I'm Agent Teresa Lisbon.
You wanted to talk to me?
Hi.
- Hi.
- Um...
Detective Elliott said
that you're in charge of the...
the Red John investigation?
That's right.
We took the case over
from Sac P.D. in May.
What's happening
with the investigation?
That's a big question, Mr. Jane
and we're a little busy right now.
Another case has come in.
Could you come back
another time?
Yeah, well, I can wait.
I-I-I'll wait.
That's not really practical. We don't
have a waiting area for guests.
I could just sit right there.
I'm sorry. It's policy.
Okay.
Policy.
Call. Make an appointment.
We'll talk as soon as possible.
- I'm afraid I have to go.
- Yeah, no problem.
I-I'm just gonna
wait outside, and, uh...
- Mr. Jane...
- No, it's okay.
It's a nice day. I'll take a walk.
And, um, if I come back
in three hours
- will that be okay?
- Sure.
Thank you.
- Hey, Steve?
- Yeah.
Would you help Mr. Jane
find his way out of the building?
Sure.
You--you work
on the Red John case?
That's none of your business, sir.
Have any suspects?
- Like I said.
- Ah. I...
It's my--my wife and daughter.
I...
Red John killed
my wife and daughter.
Oh, well, uh...
I'm very sorry for your loss.
But we don't discuss cases
with the relatives of victims.
Yeah, no. I-I understand.
Listen, no offense
but I seen a hundred guys
just like you.
You wanna find this son of a bitch
and kill him, right?
Yeah.
Well, what happens
it'll drive you crazy.
My advice? You move away.
Far away somewhere.
Forget it.
Start another family.
I know that's tough
but it's the best way.
I just asked if
there were any suspects.
One more time.
Let it go.
Come on.
What went wrong with you?
Say what?
Well, clearly, you're older and more
experienced than Agent Lisbon.
You must have done something
pretty bad
for them to promote a woman
20 years your junior over you.
Who told you that?
It's a temperament issue.
As well as character.
That's why they gave you
to Lisbon, isn't it?
Because she was new, and no one
else would work with you.
What the hell
are you doing, Hannigan?
- Boss...
- I told you to take him downstairs
not beat him up!
Sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
I-I lost it.
No, no. It--it's fine.
It's fine.
My fault. My fault entirely.
- I provoked you. I'm sorry.
- God, Hannigan, get him some ice.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Seriously, it--it's not his fault.
I-I deserved it, okay?
He is supposed to act
like a professional law officer...
at all times.
Let's get you some ice.
Come on.
Teresa Lisbon. That's a...
That's a nice name.
How did it happen?
Hannigan says he was provoked.
Mr. Jane agrees.
He says it's all his fault.
Decent of him.
A cop with a history attacks
a murder victim's grieving spouse.
Excellent.
I'm sorry, boss.
I hope we can find a way
to make this right
without being too harsh
on Hannigan.
He's a good guy, he's just
a little too old school.
Mr. Jane says
he won't press charges.
Let's hope Mr. Jane
remains so amiable
when he wakes up
in the morning
with a pounding headache
and time to think.
We must find a way
to make him happy.
Mr. Jane?
Director Virgil Minelli.
No, no, no, no. Sit.
I'm, uh, I'm terribly sorry
about all of this.
I understand that, um,
Agent Hannigan has apologized?
Uh, yes, he did.
Mm-hmm.
I hope that's been of some help.
Uh...
Um...
I-I came here to, uh,
find out about Red John.
Yes. Agent Lisbon told me.
Uh, I understand your concern.
Red John is one of the most
difficult cases we've faced.
- How many victims, Lisbon?
- Ten.
- So far.
- Yes.
Catching him is our top priority.
How many interviews
has your team done?
Over a hundred.
We're also re-analyzing
all of the physical evidence
that Sac P.D. gathered.
We're sharing some of that
with the FBI.
We're pursuing
a lot of different leads.
We haven't had a break yet
but as soon as we get one,
we'll let you know.
What are the leads?
Where are they leading?
You--you have any...
suspects?
We can't give out details
of the investigation.
You don't have any suspects.
It is a complicated investigation,
and, yes, slow.
But everything that can be done
is being done.
I'll tell you what, Mr. Jane.
My people have to get
back to work now.
Long drive ahead of 'em.
But if you don't mind
waiting here
when, uh, Agent Lisbon returns
I'm sure she'll be very happy
to show you the files
and explain the case to you.
Is it in the country?
The long drive ahead
is it--is it in the country?
Would you like to go along?
Even better.
Ride along with Lisbon.
She can answer any questions
you may have on the way.
- I'd like that.
- Good!
Hey, boss.
What's he doing here?
Long story.
- Patrick Jane. Hi.
- Cho.
- Just pretend I'm not here.
- Okay.
Victim's name is Winston Dellinger.
Shot three times.
That's his car.
Road crew came across his body
around 6:00 this morning.
Coroner estimates
he was shot around midnight.
There's some damage
on the front end.
He must have hit something
so could be a road rage type thing?
I doubt it.
There's no debris nearby.
Widen the search.
See if you can find out
where it did happen.
- All right.
- This is Lisbon.
What do you do now?
Well, techs have done
their job
took all the photos.
We get up close.
Well, you see, it looks like
he was shot right here.
Note the natural posture
of the body.
- And there's no drag marks.
- Uh-huh.
Now this guy--
this guy's pretty clean.
Pretty fresh.
Sometimes we get to them
there's so many maggots,
it looks like a stewpot boiling.
Just poppin' and bubblin'.
And the smell--oh!
Excuse me. Excuse me. Sorry.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just, uh...
Oh, I'm just a little lightheaded.
I told the coroner
they could take the body.
We need to piece together
where Dellinger was before he got here.
Work his cell phone, credit card bills.
Retrace his steps.
- Okey-dokey.
- Find the lady.
- What lady?
- The lady he was on a date with.
Wow. So you are
some kinda psychic.
How do you figure that, Kreskin?
There's no such thing as psychics.
He has a bachelor's car,
peacock clothes.
He smells of alcohol
and breath mints
and too much cologne.
Date.
Okay. Well, thank you
for your input.
Cho, you got anything?
Uniforms found a credit card
receipt in his car.
He had dinner last night
at a restaurant
called Cafe Tuscany.
Go there. See what they can
tell you about him.
The victim's father
was an appellate court judge.
I need to go and talk to him.
Roger that.
I'm headed back to Sacramento.
You want me to drop you off
somewhere on the way?
I'll go with you.
Uh, so how does this work?
I go in. Ask the people questions.
They're probably pretty upset.
May not be able to tell me much.
It doesn't help to have
other people around.
- You--you want me to stay here?
- I would prefer that.
Sure. No--no problem.
I don't--I don't want to intrude.
Agent Lisbon, do you mind
if we talk out here?
My wife's extremely distraught.
I'd rather she didn't hear us.
This is, um, Patrick Jane.
Pleasure. This way, please.
Had you and your wife heard
from your son recently?
We spoke on the phone
last week.
Was he in some sorta trouble?
Agent, I have the sickening feeling
that this had nothing
to do with Winston.
What do you mean by that?
I've put a lot of desperate individuals
into prison over the years.
Any one of them
might be behind this.
Why would they go after him?
Why not you?
You wanna hurt a man?
Don't kill him.
Kill his family.
We'll certainly look into that.
Alcoholism.
Terrible thing.
Winston was drinking again?
We won't know until after
we get the lab reports back.
So...
You're simply casting aspersions?
No. I--I just...
I assumed from your manner...
From what manner, sir?
Your disappointment in him.
With regard to my son, Mr. Jane
it's myself I'm disappointed in.
He's my failure.
Do you have a child, Mr. Jane?
No.
Well, then you wouldn't understand.
If there's nothing else,
Agent Lisbon...
No, sir.
"Dellinger chairs
the Fifth Circuit Appeals Court."
Do you know how much trouble
I could get in if he's pissed off?
- No. How much?
- A lot.
What you have to understand--
Yeah?
Hang on, Cho.
Excuse me.
Go on.
Just talked to the maître d'
at Cafe Tuscany.
Said Dellinger came in
last night with a woman.
"Said she seemed
a little low-rent."
"Dellinger got so drunk
the woman left before dinner arrived."
Really?
"Also talked to the cab company
that picked up Dellinger's date."
Her name's Kelly Burbage.
She's coming in tomorrow.
Thanks.
You were right.
The victim was on a date.
Good call.
- Cold reading.
- Cold reading?
You, for instance. You...
cared for a dysfunctional parent.
Father, probably. That's why
you put up with Hannigan.
I don't put up with Hannigan.
His unhappiness reminds you
of your father's unhappiness.
We're done for the day.
Is there somewhere
I could drop you off?
What about the Red John files?
Mr. Jane, I truly sympathize.
I understand how you're feeling.
I would probably feel the same way.
But nothing good will come
from chasing this man.
It's the kind of obsession
that destroys people.
Go someplace else.
Try to get on with your life.
That's just what Hannigan said.
Come to the office in the morning.
But clean yourself up.
You're a mess.
Get in.
Hi.
Hey.
It's Kimball Cho, isn't it?
Is that after the Kipling character?
No. Why are you still here?
Agent Lisbon told me to come by.
To read the Red John files.
- Hey.
Lisbon told him to come by.
Read the Red John files.
Hi.
All right. Hi.
Oh, pretend I'm not here.
Uh, okay.
Kelly Burbage. Girl who had dinner
with the victim.
- Interview three.
- All right. Thanks.
You can take the desk
over there.
No one's using that.
Uh, yeah.
Miss Burbage...
how do you know
Winston Dellinger?
I work tending bar
at the Thirsty Pup in Hagginwood?
- Winston's a regular.
- He has a drinking problem.
- It's a bar.
- What happened at dinner?
What I shoulda known.
He climbed through
two bottles of house red
before I even got
my pasta pomodoro.
I told him he was too drunk
to drive me home.
He got mad, I got a cab.
Look, if this is because Winston did
something last night
it's just because
he was smashed.
- He wouldn't hurt a fly.
- He's dead. He was killed last night.
What?
Somebody shot him.
About two hours
after he left the restaurant.
Any idea
who might have done that?
- Oh, my God.
- That sounds like "yes".
There's--there's this guy...
we used to date
but I broke it off because he was
this gigantic ball of negativity.
Sure.
He called me last night
after I got home.
Totally messed up.
He said he'd followed me
on the date.
He kept talking
about what a loser Winston was
- and how he didn't deserve me.
- What's his name?
Emmett.
Emmett Cox.
Hey, boss.
Cox has two arrests for assault
and a gun charge pending.
Nice.
- Is this address still current?
- Burbage thinks so.
You and Hannigan see if you can
locate him, bring him in.
Seems like a real charmer.
Full S.W.A.T. protocol.
He said you said
he was allowed to be here.
Yes, I did.
I didn't think he'd actually show up.
- Go get Cox.
- Yes, boss.
Mr. Jane!
Mr. Jane.
- You--you can call me Patrick.
- Patrick, have a seat.
You were hoping
I wouldn't come back?
Yes.
Frankly, I don't think
you should look at the files.
Your boss said I could.
You're right.
I should probably just start a new life.
I can't.
I will have the files sent up.
There's a lot of them.
Meanwhile, you stay in here.
I don't mind waiting out there.
I don't wanna be a burden.
You're kind of a distraction
to the office.
No offense, but you have a bit
of a homeless vibe about you.
I cleaned up,
like you, uh, told me to.
It's a process, huh?
Hm. Well.
- Get in here.
- Come on, Cox.
Have a seat. Go on.
Scoot up.
"There you go. That's it."
Okay, Emmett, cut the crap
and tell us what happened.
Bite me.
I done nothing wrong.
Well, if you done nothing wrong
then there's no reason
not to tell us what happened.
Give us something.
I followed Kel and that dude
to the restaurant.
Kel came out
and got in a cab.
A few minutes later,
that dude came out.
By "that dude" you mean
Winston Dellinger?
If that's his name.
He got in his car,
so I followed him.
Now why'd you do that?
Honesty, I was thinking
I'd follow him home.
Mess him up a little.
Take his money and whatnot.
But no harm, no foul, right?
Well...
Winston Dellinger's dead.
That's not on me.
The dude was driving too fast
and I couldn't keep up
so I went home.
Well, you know what I think?
I think when the dude
pulled over to relieve himself
you drove up behind him
and you thought, "Hey, cool."
"Why not jack him right here?"
"Save time, save trouble".
That's what I think.
"You can think what you like."
All I'm saying is if you will
let me go at him again
Cox will open up.
I don't know.
I think he's telling the truth.
Where are we?
I went through the threats
made against Judge Dellinger.
Doesn't look like any of these guys
have the kinda pull
to reach outta prison
and kill Winston.
What are you doing?
Uh, just stretching my legs.
Anything else?
Yeah. Ballistics came back.
Bullets in the body
match the bullets from a gun
used in an armed robbery
in Oakland 12 years ago.
Those guys are in prison.
The gun was never recovered.
- Someone else must have gotten it.
- I got something.
Nine months ago, Winston was
charged with vehicular manslaughter.
D.A. said he hit and killed a woman
named Mia Dos Santos
- while driving drunk.
- Well, what happened?
The manslaughter charge was dropped
before it went to trial.
He pleaded to a D.U.I.,
no jail time.
- Well, how does that happen?
- You got me.
Dos Santos' husband was mad
when the charge got dropped.
- He made some threats.
- Who handled the case?
Sac P.D. detective
named Nathaniel Kim.
- Talk to him. I'll talk to the husband.
- Okay.
Where are the Red John files?
They were supposed
to be here by now.
Yeah, they're on their way.
The office remodel's got
the records department backed up.
Great. Wonderful.
Tell them to get their butts in gear.
Hey. You.
You're coming with me.
"I'm looking
for Detective Nathaniel Kim."
"You got him."
I work here on my off days.
You know, Sac P.D.'s great
but alimony and child support
are a bitch.
- This about Winston Dellinger?
- That's right.
Yeah, well. Dellinger knocked poor
Mia Dos Santos right out of her shoes.
She had three kids.
That's tough.
And why did the manslaughter charge
get dropped?
We only had circumstantial evidence
putting Winston at the scene.
Nobody actually saw him hit her.
But we did have blood on his car.
Seemed like a dunk.
Lab results come back
blood doesn't belong
to Mia Dos Santos.
No dunk. No case.
We were lucky to get the D.U.I.
Did you double-check
the lab results?
Sure. Came back the same.
And Winston's father's a judge.
He knows people
all through the system.
Yes, he is, and, yes, he does.
You ever consider
the possibility he reached out
made sure his son
didn't go to prison?
Sure, I thought it.
Wouldn't say it.
Why not?
Guy's a freakin'' Tyrannosaurus rex.
I'm gonna accuse him of obstruction
of justice on a hunch?
You do it.
What can I get you?
Have you heard anything
about Winston Dellinger recently?
I heard he was killed.
Is that right?
Where did you hear that,
Mr. Dos Santos?
Not sure.
Our lawyers, I think.
You know, we were preparing
a, uh, wrongful death lawsuit
against Dellinger.
It's not gonna happen now.
And have you been in contact
with Mr. Dellinger
since your wife's death?
No. Not recently.
After the charges were dropped
didn't you seek him out,
threaten him several times?
Yeah.
I was really angry.
And I said some angry things.
I shouldn't have done that.
Stupid.
No. No, it wasn't.
That man killed my daughter.
And he left her babies
without their mother.
And nothing happens to him?
You should've done more.
You should've hurt him!
You should've hurt him
the way that he hurt us!
What have we got?
Ran Christian Dos Santos.
No arrests, but he's had trouble
at work since his wife died.
Issues with customers. He's taking
an anger management course.
- And what about the judge?
- We checked his bank accounts.
No significant money transfers
when the murder charge was withdrawn.
If he paid someone off,
there's no sign of it.
Still no sign of where
Winston Dellinger's car
had an accident
the night he was killed.
There's some uniforms out there
looking for debris.
That's it?
Well, it's a hard case, boss.
Let's start from the top.
Bring in everybody
involved in the case.
We'll hear their stories again.
- Maybe something will shake loose.
- Will do.
First batch of Red John.
Where do you want 'em?
Uh, you can just leave it there.
Eager beaver, huh?
Mr. Jane
before you get into that
I wanted to ask a favor.
I need your help.
Okay. Everybody involved in
the Dellinger murder is in that room.
One of them is very likely lying.
One of them is very likely
the murderer.
Wow.
What I'd like you to do
is go in there
take a look at all of them
and tell me if you can spot the liar.
- Me?
- You seem to have a gift.
I told you, I'm not a psychic.
I'm a charlatan.
You hear me?
I-I-I'm a fraud.
I believe you.
But whatever it is, it's a gift.
I figure, why not use it?
- I can't.
- We're kind of at a standstill here.
Come on.
Hello, everybody.
Um, this is Patrick Jane.
He's a consultant with the CBI.
Before we start the interviews
he's gonna... we'll see
what he's gonna do.
Mr. Jane?
Hi, folks.
Quick question--which one of you
killed Winston Dellinger?
- Oh, come on. This is ridiculous.
- What?
- I'm not gonna sit here and listen to this.
- Is he serious?
Everybody just calm down, please.
That was worth a try.
Uh, Agents Cho and Rigsby
will proceed with the interviews.
Thank you very much.
- Judge, if you'll come with me.
- Uh, wait a minute.
- I think I know who did it.
- You sure?
Pretty sure.
If everybody could just
please sit back down.
My apologies. Please.
Now what?
- You are absolutely sure?
- Uh, 70%.
You have tarot cards?
- Tarot cards?
- No.
Uh, ladies and gentlemen,
um, I-I'm sorry
for, uh, for wasting your time.
- If, uh...
- I've had more than enough of this.
Agent Lisbon, really?
This is outrageous.
- Tell him, Judge.
- Just one moment more.
There's something
I wanna show you.
Something you might
find amazing.
I used to be a psychic.
I used to read minds, talk to dead people.
Only I didn't.
Of course I didn't,
'cause there's no such thing
as psychics or mediums,
or at least I've never met one.
Psychic powers are just tricks.
They're mind games.
It's observation.
But it works.
There's a killer in this room
and I'm gonna use
pseudo-psychic powers
to persuade that killer
to confess.
This is bull.
Shortcut method--the first person
to leave did it.
Now like I say, there's
no such thing as psychics.
Let's be clear about that.
But the human mind
is amazingly powerful.
It can do things for real
that sometimes feel like magic.
And I wanna show you.
Now, normally, I would use
Tarot cards for this.
But, uh, in this case,
these will have to do
as long as you're all willing
to use a little imagination.
Bear with me.
Agent Lisbon, if you could, uh...
mix those cards up
thoroughly, please.
Thank you for your patience.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Now...
I would like you, without looking
to choose a card,
face-down, but first--
and this is very important--
before you take the card
I'd like you to close your eyes
and I'd like you to think
about the last scary dream you had.
Remember the last time
you woke up
shivering with fear.
Got it? Good.
Thank you. Open your eyes.
Take a card.
Keep it face-down.
Keep your hand on top of it.
Thank you.
Now here's the thing--
you think you just made
a random pick.
Where, in fact, your subconscious mind
made a very meaningful choice.
And this is how the killer
will be revealed.
Mrs. Recinos
you dreamt that your daughter
was falling into a very dark place
and you couldn't stop her.
You called out that you loved her
but she couldn't hear you.
- Yes.
- And that's why you chose the lovers.
Judge Dellinger,
you dreamt of death.
And you chose death.
Kelly, you can't shake the idea
that you'll never find true love.
And you picked the fool.
How do you do that?
Mr. Kim.
You have a lot of scary dreams.
But you can't remember them.
However, you're a cop.
So you think the rules
don't apply to you.
And you chose the magician.
- Neat trick.
- Yes, just a trick.
Mr. Dos Santos, you dream
of being trapped.
Caged like an animal.
And you dream of a terrible,
violent escape.
You picked the devil.
None of that's true.
And, Mr. Cox.
You constantly dream
of all the people you've hurt
coming back to seek revenge.
And guess what?
They have the same dream.
You chose the hanged man.
Uh, actually that's not... right.
Uh, Mr. Kim had that card.
Ah.
Uh-huh.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means you killed
Winston Dellinger.
- Yeah, right. Give me a break.
- No. No break. You did it.
The subconscious mind
never lies.
Your guilt is written
on that card...
- and written all over your face.
- No.
No, I-I didn't. Come on.
It's a card trick.
Yes, it was, but when I said
I could use your choice of card
to reveal the killer,
you looked a little worried.
For a split second.
Just you.
And then you looked relieved
when I couldn't read your dream.
And then when you saw
the hanged man
- the blood drained from your face.
- No.
- No, this is ridiculous.
- Everyone can see your guilt.
But what I can't see
is your motive.
Why, Nathaniel?
Why did you kill him?
Look at me.
Why, Nathaniel?
You seem like a good person.
You come from good people.
Why'd you kill him?
Well, I'll be damned.
That's your man, Agent Lisbon.
That's your man.
You had the evidence
against Winston Dellinger.
I went to the lab.
I swapped the blood sample
from his fender
for another sample.
Why'd you do it?
I'm a silent partner in the bar.
Everything I got is in that place.
Last year, we got sued.
- Guy got beat up in a fight.
- And the bar lost the suit?
I was gonna lose
every penny I had.
But when I caught
the Dellinger case
I found out his father would hear
the appeal of the lawsuit.
The judge must have been scared
about his son going to prison?
Yeah. Terrified.
I mean, he was sure
the kid would be killed
'cause of all the guys
he put away.
So I went to the judge
and made a deal.
He'd rule in the bar's favor
I'd hide the evidence
against Winston.
How did that
get Winston killed?
That night, I'm in bed, asleep.
And Winston calls me
in a drunken panic.
He says he was driving
and hit somebody... again.
I said he should man up
and call the cops.
He says if I don't help him
he'll tell about the deal
I made with his father.
I mean, he was gonna destroy
my career.
"So I go out
to the place to meet him."
"Look, I hit him right there."
"Oh, my car."
"Look, he must have crawled
off the road or some--"
"Well, don't just stand there,
help me!"
"You owe me! My dad saved your ass!
Now do something!"
"He's freaking out. I mean,
he can't find the body."
"He thinks maybe
whoever he hit"
"is still alive
and crawled away."
"I mean... he was outta control."
"It's gotta be here somewhere."
"And that's when I knew."
"It's gotta be here."
"If I don't do something
about this fool, right now..."
"Winston."
"He's gonna dog me
the rest of my life."
"Sorry."
You, uh, you ever find
the guy he hit?
Must be still out there somewhere.
No.
But uniforms found a deer
that had been hit by a car
a little ways off the road.
Must have been too drunk
to know the difference.
A deer?
He hit a... a deer?
That's perfect.
So Minelli really hired
this Jane guy?
Well, he exposed a corrupt cop
dethroned a judge.
Those are all major points
for us.
As far as Minelli's concerned,
he's a hero.
And, uh...
does Hannigan know about this?
Yeah. He doesn't wanna work
with Jane
so he's transferring
to another unit.
Any idea who's gonna replace Hannigan?
Don't know yet. There's a new class
of trainees coming up.
Maybe we'll get one of them.
Files are right there
if you wanna take a look.
Like this one.
She's cute. And outta your league.
One last time--
are you sure
you wanna do this?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay. I tried.
You did.
Thank you.
Shall we go?
Here you go.
I'm going home. If you need me
to explain anything, give me a call.
Yes?
"Virgil Minelli?"
Yes. Who's this?
Alexa Shultz, FBI.
We met at the forensics conference
in Roanoke.
Director Shultz.
What a pleasure to hear from you.
I understand the CBI
has hired a new consultant.
A man named Patrick Jane?
"Yes."
I'm surprised you know.
I didn't realize you followed
our hiring that closely.
Mr. Jane is connected
to a case we're interested in.
The serial killer known
as Red John.
"I'm, um, calling to ask a favor."
What's that?
I would appreciate updates
on the Red John case.
"That way, when my boss
asks me what's going on"
"I have something to tell him."
To put it bluntly, Alexa
why would I do that?
"What's in it for me?"
It's useful to have a friend
in the FBI, isn't it?
"And I'm a good friend."
Well, I'm a great believer
in inter-agency cooperation.
"I don't see why
we couldn't engage in some."
I look forward to it, Virgil.
Oh, by the way
one thing you might wanna know
about Patrick Jane--
you know how he's been
outta sight in the past year?
"You know where he's been?"
No.
An insane asylum.
Good luck.
Done.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Hey, boss.
We caught one. Fresno.
Get Rigsby.
Let's leave before traffic.
Okay.